John N. Rowe III papers, Inclusive: 1510-1989, undated, Bulk: 1830-1880
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Early Texas Documents, 1801-1989, undated; 2
  - Legal, 1801-1924, undated; 2
    - Legal: Menard, Michael B., Eleanor Payne Frankland, 1847 January 23 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Menard, M. B., James Love, Levi Jones, Samuel M. Williams, A. F. James, 1847 March 25 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Menard, Michael B., John Mclean, Charles & Thomas B. Power, Alfred F. James, 1848 July 1 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Menard, M. B., John S. Roberts, Frederick Phillips, Leon Dyer, 1849 November 29 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Menard, Michael B., T. F. Hollis, 1853 July 9 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Menard, Michael B., Curtis S. Swann, Richard B. Dawson, John L. Darragh, 1855 April 17 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Menefee, John T., 1873 February 2 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Midkiff, Susana, Josiah Frazier Crosby, 1838 December 29 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Millard, Henry and Joshua Shaw, 1842 December (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Millard, Col. Henry, Col. George Washington Hockley, 1842 December 6 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Millbank, Robert W., Isaac M. Millbank, Warrick Martin, 1854 May 4 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Millbank, Robert W., Warrick Martin, Edward C. Payne, Levi Jones, 1856 June 11 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Miller, Daniel, Henry S. Brown, Francis S. Hubby, 1872 May 28 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Miller, Diana, Patrick Reels, 1841 October 13 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Miller, James B., Robert McCreery, 1848 July 8 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Miller, Peter, 1854 March (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Miller, Washington D., 1848 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Mills, ?, 1854 November (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John B. Ashe, John W. Jockusch, 1855 May 10 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John W. Jockusch, J. P. Walton, George W. Tuggle, 1854 December 29, 1855 June 13 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John W. Joskusch, J. P. Walton, George W. Tuggle, 1855 March 22 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, J. W. Jockusch, John B. Ashe & Wife, 1855 May 10 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John W. Jockusch, Isaiah King, 1855 June 11 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John W. Jockusch, J. P. Walton, George W. Tuggle, 1855 June 13 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, Johnston & Dewbery, 1855 June 15 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, Alexander S. Johnston, John Dewbery, 1856 June 5 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John W. Jockusch, John Findley, Alexander A. Cameron, 1856 August 1 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, John W. Jockusch, 1856 December 22 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Mills, Robert, Moses Parks, 1845 May 9 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Mitchell, Andrew, 1867 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Mitchell, Charles, David D. Atchison, 1853 October 31 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Mitchell, Charles, 1854 March 31 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Mitchell, Charles, D. D. Atchison, 1855 February (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Mitchell, William J., John I. Holt, 1853 September 13 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Mixon, Nahan, Robert Brotherton, 1838 November 1 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Moffatt, Robert, George W. L. Bond, O. C. Hartley, John S. Sydnor Hyacinthe de St. Cyr, 1851 July 12 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Moore, Alexander, Isaac Fessender, 1853 July 6 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Moore, Alfred, Charles Lockhart, 1842 December 15 (Box 22, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Moore, Francis and Hamilton Stuart, 1841 May (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Moore, Francis, John P. Borden, Hiram Close, Amos A. Turner, 1841 May 4 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Moore, J. W., Julius Frederich, 1848 February 17 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Moore, James W., John S. Jones, 1858 August 21 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Moore, James W., Thomas F. McKinney, Samuel M. Williams, J. C. Kuhn, Stephen W. Tichenor, Pinckney Henderson, 1846 July 4 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Legal: Moore, James W. and Williams, Edward H., 1849 July (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Legal: Moreau, Stephen, W. C. Duffield, 1851 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - Legal: Morgan, Antonio, Allen Lewis, John Prevara, 1847 January 25 (Box 22, Folder 80)
    - Legal: Morgan, Antonio, John Perera, 1847 January 25 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Legal: Morgan, Antonio, John B. Perera, 1847 February 12 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Legal: Morgan, Antonio and John Perara, 1847 April (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Legal: Morgan, James, G. B. Jamieson, 1834 November 21 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Morgan, Theodore, M. Buchanan, 1854 May 31 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Morris, William, C. L. Lewis, Moseley Baker, 1838 June 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Morris, William and Margaret McLane, John McCullough, 1839 January 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Muller, Frederick W., E. L. Ufford, 1846 April 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Muller, Peter, 1854 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Mumford, Jane B. Ferdinand S. Mumford, 1853 June 10 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Mumford, Jane B., Ferdinand Mumford, 1853 June 10 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Munson, David, George Morris and William Robertson, 1845 October (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Musack, Miles, John Bevil, W. H. Stark and A. G. Parker, 1839 August (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Myers, Livingston L., 1848 May (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Nash, George, Lent M. Hitchcock, 1847 November 24 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Nash, James P., Edward Francis Byrne, Thomas M. Joseph, 1856 January 28 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Legal: [illegible] Nash, A. Hotchkiss, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Natious, Joseph, S. M. Baird, 1842 September 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Neal, Benjamin F., Edwin B. Settle, 1844 December 28 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Neely, Richard E., Robert Duren and Sam Hobson, 1839 July (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Neill, John A., Alonzo B. Swtizer, 1840 January 2 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Nelson, Fannie S., 1884 May 3 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Nelson, George, George Hinson & Wife, 1882 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Neville, Albert M.-Louisiana, 1865 June 5 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Newell, Stewart, 1847 March 20 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Newell, Stewart, 1847 April 27 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Newell, Stewart, William Douglass, 1840 August 18 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Newell, Stewart, Pizarro Edmunds, William D. Lee, 1841 February 23 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Nobbitt, John., David Rusk, Charles Chevaillier, 1839 December 31 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Nordman, Lewis E. amd G. A. Tuss, 1846 November (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Norris, James M., Joseph Osterhunt, 1854 October 6 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Norton, M. P., Joseph A. Perkins, John Delesdenier, 1846 October 13 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Oakey, Samuel W., John H. Bennett, 1845 August 25 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Oakey, Samuel W., William Bryan, 1847 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Obar, John, Nancy Obar, 1850 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Obar, John, 1851 April 29 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Obar, Nancy, John Obar, 1849 June (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Legal: O’Brian, John, Edward L. Bernard, 1841 February 8 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Legal: O’Bryan, Fed., J. N. Lightfoot, 1875 November 24 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Legal: O’Neil, Joseph, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Osterman, Joseph, J. H. and Caroline Sylvester, 1847 June 11 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Orton, Colonel., H. M. Trueheart, 1859 December (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Owens, A. J. J., 1862 February (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Pace, Dempsey C., William J. Jones, Edward Flemming, C. Windrow, 1850 October 1 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Pace, Wesley W., Fenton M. Gibson, 1838 July 2 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Pace, Wesley W., [Illegible] Menard, 1838 October 29 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Pace, William, 1857 January 5 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Page, J., Samuel Maas, Benjamin S. Parsons, 1855 May 31 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Palmer & Luce, et al, Harris & Lacy, 1851 December 24 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Palmer & Luce, et al, Harris & Lacy, S. A. White & Co., William A. Wandell, E. O. Lynch, 1851 December 17 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Palmer, J. F., 1839 November 21 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Palmer, Samuel, Harris & Lacy, A. B. Leavitt, Palmer & Luce, E. O. Lynch, 1854 November 23 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Pape, Frederich and Dorothea Schumacher, 1846 April (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Paracovitch, Joseph, 1842 August 25 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Parcovitch, Joseph, 1842 August 26 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Paris, P. and John Pratt, 1840 March (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Parish, T. R., Robert H. Ision, 1877 September 26 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Parke, Ellen, 1850 August (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Parke, Ellen and James W. Moore, 1850 December (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Parker, Charles, 1840 December 21 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Parker, William, James Dolin, Leander Wescott, Catherine Baker, C. F. Worcester, 1839 July (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Parker, William W., Beaumont & Dunbar, 1840 February 27 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Parkes, Elianes, 1844 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Parmalee, Richard, E. G. Harris, Mary Harris, William Sturrock, Daniel Rusk, “Decision in Court Case Mary Harris vs William Sturrock”, 1839 May 21 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Parmalee, Richard, William B. Ochitree, Charles M. Walters, Benjamin A. Vansickle, David Lacy, David Rusk, Robert Walters, Moses Barnes, Thomas B. Garrett, Samuel Bell, James C. Hill, Albert A. Nelson, L. M. Aston, “Petition to Step Survey of Lands”, 1844 October 7 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Parmer, A. C., Martin Parmer, 1840 January 13 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Parr, Mary, 1854 April (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Parr, Mary, 1854 May (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Parsons, Benjamin S., Robertson, Holt, and Atchison, 1852 September 14 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Parsons, Benjamin S., James Sorley, undated (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Parsons, Samuel, Cyrus Smith, A. Hitchcock, C. T. Plimpton, John A. Formwalt, John S. Martin, 1857 July (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Pascovitch, Joseph M., John M. Dor and Jacob Sasse, 1841 December (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Patton, Robert S., M. L. Patton, John S. Berry, Steamboat Uncle Ben, 1856 November 15 (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Paul, James, [illegible] Robertson, 1853 August 4 (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Paullalair, C., undated (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Paulus, Frederick & Mary, 1860 March (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Payne, Alva, James H. Holt, 1846 December 2 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Pendleton, Jame W., 1944 November (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Pendleton, William, 1844 December (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Legal: Penny, Thomas, Moseley Baker, 1845 November 21 (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Legal: Peters, Lewis H., William Watts, 1843 November 29 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Petition for County Precinct at Walnut Springs, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Pettit, David L., Robert Pettit, 1852 October 21 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Philip, Henrich, Wilhelm Stoffregen, 1846 July 7 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Phillips, G. E., 1841 June (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Phillips, James W., 1918 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Phillips, Moro, John E. Jeffers, 1840 October 3 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Phillips, Moro, Alfred F. James, David R. Robertson, 1840 November 9 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Pieper, Elizabeth, Peter Rapencup and Samuel J. Redgate, 1839 April (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Pilante, Josiah H., James B. Badger, D. N. Terheun, J. M. Allen, 1845 January 25 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Pilant, Joseph, 1859 February 19 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Pilant, J. Willie, 1859 July, 1861 April (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Pilants, J. W., 1861 June (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Pinkaro, Ferdinand, John D. Vertner, 1840 September 30 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Piper, Elizabeth, Kasper Simon, 1838 December 31 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Pitcher, Symann, 1847 October (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Plat No. A.—City of Nacogdoches, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Pollock, Robert and James Foreman, 1839 November (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Pollock, Robert and James Foreman, 1839 November (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Pollock, Robert and James Foreman, 1840 January and November (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Pollock, Robert, James Foreman and A. B. Weldiman, 1840 January (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Port of Galveston Customs Slip, 1836 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Porter, Royal A., Levi Jones, 1850 November 29 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Potter, Mark Milton, Mordecai Primrose, 1855 December 26 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Powell, Charley, 1871 July 27 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Power, Charles, James Nelson, Benjamin F., 1851 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Powers, Charles vs. Henry Terrell, Estate of B. F. Stockton, 1845 July 30 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Powers vs. Terrell, 1845 November (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Prescott, Eustes, Samuel Jones, 1847 June 8 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Prescott, Eustis, Charles Vyse, 1848 June 21 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Preston, Thomas H., 1838 March 15 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Prevara, John, Antonio Morgan, 1847 January 25 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Prichards and Thomas C. Woodby, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Prickett, W. R. and J. Posildard, 1819 October (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Primrose & Rhoden, 1855 June 5 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Primrose, Mordecai, William B. Roden, Elisha O. Lynch, 1856 June 16, 1856 June 18 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Primrose, Mordecai, [Illegible] Rodin, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Proclamation, San Antonio, 1890 September (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Legal: Pullen, T. J., R. T. Gassoway, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Quick, Edmund, Theodore Quick, 1842 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Quimby, James M., George M. Spencer, Augustus R. Ball, Blake Little, John H. Little, 1856 August 26 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Quirk, Edward, 1838 November 14 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Ralston, Cleveland, 1847 December 17 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Ramsey, J. W., Poewll R. Edwards, Alfred F. James, James H. Sylvester, 1848 February 14 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Ramsey, John, 1850 November 26 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Ramkin, Samuel and Jonathan E. Blair, 1843 September (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Rape, Henry, Milton Mash, 1881 August 7 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Ravana, Manuel, Mateo Gutierritz, Antonio Morgan, J. B. Perara, 1848 April 26 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Reed, Charles A., Benjamin B. Peck, David Hodges, 1851 May 13 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Reed, M. B., Jacob Mask, John Recter, Jackson Recter, B. J. Thompson, Neil Martin, Joseph Nations, Archibald Hotchkiss, L. R. Peck, “Court Order for Arrest”, 1836 September 8 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Reed, John N., Lent M. Hitchcock, Jr., Samuel M. Williams, Henry B. Andrews, 1852 August 21 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Reed, John N., Henry B. Martin, 1857 March 21 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Reed, William, William Hill, Williamson & Vail and Phineas G. Merritt, 1851 September (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Reels, Mary, 1841 October 13 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Reppien, Carl, John G. Brock, J. E. Rump, 1852 June 28 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Republic of Texas, Blank Auditor’s Certificates, circa 1800s (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Republic of Texas Militia Officers Muster Roll, 1836 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Republic of Texas, District Court of Nacogdoches, 1839 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Rhea, John L., 1847 March 10 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Rhea, John S., O. S. Beers, Robert W. Smith, 1848 November 25 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Rhodes, E. A., John S. Sydnor, M. Hopkins, E. Andrews, 1844 October 8 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Riddle, John B., Eliza A. Cramer, 1858 May 11 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Rishen, William E., Circa 1866-1867 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Ritter, Frederick, Galveston Steam Ferry and Tow Boat Company, 1853 November 30 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Roberts, James, William B. Nichols, 1839 November 12 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Roberts, John S., Frank T. Phillips, John S. Sydnor, 1848 November 22 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Roberts, John S., L. S. Philips, John S. Sydnor, P & Cobb, undated (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Roberts, John S., Frederick T. Phillips, Leon Dyer, undated (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Robertson, David R., John M. Dor, Moro Phillips, 1840 November 3 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Robertson, J. E., Willard Richardson, 1839 December 21 (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Robertson, John, Robertson, Channy A. and James Paul, 1853 August (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Robertson, John, 1856 October (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Robertson, John, 1855 May (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Roberston, Sterling C., M. H. Steele, 1835 November 25 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Robertson, Sterling C., 1842 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Robinson, Jessy, 1884 September 30 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Robinson, John, 1855 May (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Robinson, Nancy, 1857 April (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Robinson, Nancy and Nancy Ann Hall, 1852 July (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Robinson, S. A., J. S. Underwood, 1849 August 27 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Robinson, Samuel S. and Harriet Mathew, James Huckins, 1841 September 26 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Robinson, Sarah A., J. S. Underwood, 1850 October 4 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Rodan, William B., 1855 June (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Rofs, J. J., 1845 August (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Rogers, Timothy H., undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Rose, C., 1856 February (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Rose, Charlie and Jacob Sasse, 1852 May (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Rose, Charles and Jacob Sasse, 1853 May (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Rosenberg, Henry, J. Burbank, J. H. Shindler, 1851 May 22 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Rosenberg, Henry, Thomas M. Joseph, J. H. Shindler, 1851 July 3 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Rossignol, Charles, William K. Weston, I. G. Hasbrook, 1847 May 20 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Ruthven, A. S., James Willie, James R. Jenkins, 1856 May 14 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Legal: De St. Cyr, Hyacinth, The Galveston Company, 1853 May 26 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Samuel A. White & Co., Robert A. Harris, William C. Lacy, S. A. Palmer, John A. Luce, 1851 March 19 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Sanderson, Edmund, Herman Heinroth, 1848 August 14 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Legal: Sanderson, Edmund, Herman Heinroth, 1848 November 16 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Sanderson, Harvey, Robert D. Johnson, 1841 May 8 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Legal: Sanderson, William, Thomas M. Joseph, 1850 October 30 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Legal: Sandusky, William C. and Jane M. Knight, Isaac J. Henderson, 1842 September 1 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Sargeant, Jasper. William Lewis, James Hudson, 1843 October 19 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, 1849 June 1 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, Charles Rose, 1852 May 1 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, Charles Rose, 1852 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, David Harvey, 1849 October 4 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, Mary Lee Harvey, 1850 June 4, 11, 13 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, Mary Lee Harvey, 1850 June 21 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, George Murray, James Magan, Thomas W. Marshall, 1850 July 29 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Legal: Sasse, Jacob, A. T. Lynn, May Lee Harvey, John Griffin, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Legal: Saubach, John and John S. Jones, 1855 September (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Legal: Schoenberger, Gill, David S. Kelsey, 1847 November (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Legal: Schneider, Caroline, Frederick Schneider, 1837 August 26 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - S Legal: Sea, J. N., William P. Ballinger & Thomas Jack, 1859 June 28 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Legal: Seague, Thomas M., John DeYoung, 1848 April 5 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Legal: Seawell, Mary, Buckley & Byrne, 1856 September 18 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Legal: Seekill, John, Benjamin F. Hill, Henderson Waller, W. W. Munson, H. L. Upshire, 1836, 1850 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Legal: Seeligson, Michael and Victor Girardin, 1859 March (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Legal: Seins, Allen, 1879 November (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Sellars, N., J. H. Murray, 1858 April 26 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Legal: Sellers, John, Charles L. Lewis, Jacob K. Beaumont, 1838 December 3 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Legal: Settlefield, Job G., G. W. Eaton, J. Pinckney Henderson, 1841 February 23 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Legal: Sewell, Maria, E. Walbridge, 1849 October 1 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Legal: Shaw, Joshua C., Stephen Vansickle, Lent M. Hitchcock and George H. Delesdenier, 1851 May 31 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Legal: Shaw, Joshua C., H. J. Offutt, Benjamin C. Franklin, 1850 December 31 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Legal: Shaw, J. C. and Emily Marston, 1855 December (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Legal: Shaw, Joshua C., James P. Collins, Sam S. Green, Green Harding & Co., and Tremont House, 1856 July (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Legal: Shelby, Anthony B. and William N. Sparks, 1850 August (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Legal: Sheldon, Thomas, Horace Palmer, 1838 November 7 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Legal: Sherwood & Goddard, 1855 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Legal: Silverside, Robert and William Goulborn, 1843 February (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Legal: Silvey, James E., William Watts, 1842 July 25 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Legal: Simon, Casper, Elizabeth Pieper, Peter Pieper and S. J. Reagate, 1849 August (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Legal: Simon, Casper, Elizabeth Pieper, Peter Pieper and Samuel J. Regate, 1849 June (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Legal: Simpson, William M., William Hollis, 1854 April (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Legal: Sims, Isham (Isam), 1840 August 8 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Legal: Sims, Isham (Isam), 1842 September 8 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Legal: Sims, Isham (Isam), 1843 February 11 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Legal: Sims, Isham, 1848 October (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Legal: Sims, Isham, 1848 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Legal: Sims, Isham, 1855 August 28 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Legal: Sims, Nancy, Isham (Isam) Sims, 1840 June 29 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Legal: Sims, [illegible], 1841 March (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Legal: Slaughter, Pamelia, J. B. Collinsworth, 1845 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Legal: Slaughter, Thomas S., Nancy Slaughter, 1838 September 5 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Legal: Slaughter, Thomas, William F. Clives and Slaughter Family Members (minors), 1840s (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Legal: Sleight, John S., Jonas Butler and Oscar Farish, 1849 February (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Legal: Sleight, John S., Horace Baldwin, Eliza Merritt, 1852 May 28 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Legal: Smith, Adam, Moses D. Dickey, 1839 September 9 (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Legal: Smith, George M., 1918-1919 (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - Legal: Smith, H. B., 1852 January (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - Legal: Smith, J. M., 1850 April 2 (Box 25, Folder 77)
    - Legal: Smith, James M. and Peter Bays, 1845 January (Box 25, Folder 78)